{
    "subject": "resource/Giallo",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Italian_literature",
    "human_readable": "Giallo is about Italian literature.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9000688195228577,
            "question": "What distinguishes Giallo from other genres of Italian literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7259870767593384,
            "question": "What type of literature is Giallo associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5848016738891602,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in Giallo literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5623689889907837,
            "question": "Has Giallo influenced other literary genres or forms of storytelling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49820274114608765,
            "question": "Where does the literary genre Giallo originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39068803191185,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a famous Giallo novel or author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34577322006225586,
            "question": "What is the historical context surrounding the emergence of Giallo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27841395139694214,
            "question": "How has Giallo evolved over time in terms of its themes and style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2734193205833435,
            "question": "How is Giallo typically characterized in terms of plot and suspense?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16655127704143524,
            "question": "Are there any notable films or television series inspired by Giallo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giallo is about Italian literature.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7499_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Giallo typically characterized in terms of plot and suspense?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7499_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Giallo evolved over time in terms of its themes and style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7499_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical context surrounding the emergence of Giallo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7499_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7499_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that giallo is associated with Italian literature and cinema. They describe giallo as a 20th-century Italian genre of literature and film, detailing its origins in Italian pulp novels and its significance in Italian culture."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}